<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Kevin Fan</title>
    <link>https://kevfan.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Kevin Fan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 16:32:12 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kevfan.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Managing HTTP Connections in Go: Preventing Go Routine Leaks</title>
      <link>https://kevfan.github.io/posts/go-routine-leak-http-connections/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 16:32:12 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kevfan.github.io/posts/go-routine-leak-http-connections/</guid>
      <description>Motivation While working on a Go service, I encountered an intriguing problem: a goroutine leak caused by unclosed HTTP connections. This issue was challenging to reproduce as it only occurred when a specific service utilized Resty and custom HTTP transport options while interacting with our service. Delving deeper into the intricacies of managing HTTP connections, I realized the criticality of diligently checking and managing these connections. This blog post aims to shed light on this problem and emphasize the importance of managing HTTP connections to prevent goroutine leaks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Javalin &amp; Flyway</title>
      <link>https://kevfan.github.io/posts/javalin-flyway/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 21:48:22 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kevfan.github.io/posts/javalin-flyway/</guid>
      <description>Motivation Some time ago, while working on a college assignment using Javalin, I encountered some labs that required running SQL statements manually on the database before deploying the application to Heroku. This was a tedious task that had to be repeated every time there were changes or additions to the tables. Although I knew about Flyway and its ability to automate database migrations, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find any tutorial on the Javalin site that explained how to use it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
